now blurred the hell
take 1 bus
I came to Sao Paulo
try to put that plan 2 into action right now brother
at the same time
the effort I can talk to a little guy
i can pit and talk to a big guy
who knows
create an opportunity
someone interested in my brand
is on
I'm with the little brownies here in the backpack
and i will try to talk to João havid brother
I see what's going to happen bro
hi all good
this is where you measure
I want to talk to João
Charlie Brown
call you here o
thank you
is 1/1 brownie in skate wheel shape from Brazil is
I found 1 Charlie brownie in the hand of the Mines at reception
let's hope they receive me there right bro
if it gives
well i take off the cap brother
time stopped here guy and no return yet
I'll wait a little longer then
are you listening to me
I didn't put the crazy
I said I want to talk to João like this
I said the wrong name
it's eric chibata
forgive me
they only gave me the name of João who owns it,
right there
I think so
I don't know him bro
maybe you can be thinking like this
bro this is crazy brother
like you do things like that
that's why things don't work out for me
because i try
it's on hand
will not be possible
closed then
bye bye pra
you worth
so it was already bro
I am this guy bro
I'mous
I'm creative
I want to go to the heads
dream small
big dream
say it's the same thing
brother beauty
record myself can't record me here o
take the bus and get outside
cheerleader
missed the bus bro